



Profile

Full Stack Developer

Experienced full-stack developer, who tackles high-level tasks, meets tight deadlines and delivers consistently outstanding performances. Possesses profound knowledge in web services and cloud-based services. Exhibits strong self-taught skills, excellent team-working and communication skills. Core competencies includes:

Web Development - RESTful API Design - Ruby on Rails - HTML5/ CSS3 - Javascript - Responsive Design - Continuous Integration.

Experience

Oct 2015 - present

Research Assistant, CCIS Department, Aalto University

Research into Internet of Things topic.

Skills gained: IT Solutions, Self Motivated, Presentation Skills

<u>Sep 2013 — Aug 2015</u>

Senior Web Developer, VCCloud Department, VC Corp

- Developing web application and RESTful web services for VCCloud's Cloud Computing System, being involved in both back-end and front-end development.
- Deploying and maintaining VCCloud's web servers.

Skills gained: Team Leading, RESTful API Design, Documentation, Deployment, CI

Mar 2013- Jul 2014

Research Assistant, International Institute for Computational Science and Engineering, Hanoi University of Science and Technology

- Working in a research project on Cloud Computing technologies, being responsible for implementing a cloud computing infrastructure.
- Designing, Developing, deploying and maintaining web application services for cloud computing system BKCloud.

Skills gained: Research Skills, Cloud Computing, Web-based Service Architecture

<u>Jul 2012 – Jul 2013</u>

Web Developer, Framgia, Inc.

- Developing websites, undertaking a considerable amount of projects.
- Developing IOS, Android mobile applications.

Skills gained: Ruby on Rails, Web Development, UI/UX, Independent Working

Education

<u>2015 — Present</u>

Master in Computer Science, Aalto University, Finland

- Majoring in Web Technologies and Applications
- Honours Programme Participant.

2009 - 2014

Engineer in Information Technology, Hanoi University of Science and Technology, Vietnam

- Major in Information Technology.
- Very Good Degree.
- GPA: 8.76/10 1st rank in ICT programme cohort 54

Language Skills

Mother tongue(s)

Vietnamese

Other language(s)

English — Proficient User

Technical Skills

	Years Experience	Skill Level
Languages		
Ruby	4	Advanced
HTML5/CSS3	4	Advanced
Javascript	4	Advanced
Python	2	Intermediate
Frameworks		
Ruby/Rails	4	Advanced
Javascript/Jquery	4	Advanced
Javascript/AngularJS	2	Intermediate
PHP/WordPress	2	Novice
Databases		
MySQL	4	Advanced
PostgresSQL	4	Advanced
MongoDB	2	Intermediate
Redis	2	Intermediate